it's the first day of the month and you
see the magic words flashing on your
mobile screen your salary has been
credited your monthly income matters to
you the most as it lets you take care of
your living and household
expenses a part of it goes in
celebrating special occasions with your
family and fulfilling your big and small
wishes and the rest goes either into
savings or Investments to take care of
the bigger goals of life it's the life
you are living right now but there would
come a time when you will retire from
your work and the regular income will
take a
halt are you prepared for it will you be
able to live a lifestyle of your choice
post
retirement well to a achieve it then you
have to plan now introducing National
pension system by ICI credential pension
fund company point of presence a pension
scheme introduced by the government of
India and regulated by
pfrda the plan builds your retirement
Kitty and also helps you live a
lifestyle of your choice post
retirement let us now understand the few
few of the Salient features of
NPS the plan offers easy onboarding
where you can open your account with
ICICI credential pension fund company
point of presence
easily and get a permanent retirement
account number pan a unique number that
will last a
lifetime it also offers the flexibility
to choose investment options suiting
your needs and risk appetite and a
seamless portability of the account
across jobs and locations with NPS you
can also get additional tax benefits of
up to 10% of annual basic salary under
Section 80 ccd2 and up to 50,000 Rupees
under Section 80ccd 1B over and above
1.5 black under Section
ATC all this with the transparency of
investment norms and regular monitoring
of Fund performance by NPS
trust now let's understand this plan in
detail this is Mr Rahul he is 30 years
old and Mr Amit who is 35 years old and
both of them invest 2,500 rupees per
month in NPS till 60 years of age so
they total investment will be 34 lakh
rupees and 22 lakh rupees
respectively now at the end of the
tenure Mr Rahul will receive an NPS
Corpus of 1.6 CR rupees with a total tax
savings of 10 lakh Rupees during the
tenure and Mr Amit gets a cus of 80 lakh
rupees with a total tax savings of 7
lakh rupees dur during the tenure Mr
Rahul decides to invest early which gets
him the maximum return and security of
guaranteed income after his retirement
when it comes to securing your
retirement the earlier you start the
better so start planning today to save
more and enjoy
more for more information call our
representative today